Hey guys, welcome back.
What I've learned in the last 10 minutes
has taken me more than three hours to really create,
okay, three, three and a half hours.
It has taken me to conceptualize, try, create and,
and present it to you in short 10 minutes.
So information is really condensed.
I'm giving you literally chocolates here, okay?
Just to consume, just do
what I've been doing in the last video.
If you have not done it yet, take down the steps
and notes, just repetitive the interview, okay?
As you will, you will be able
to really fly through the interview.
What I just covered is code enough,
but there are some additional concepts which are,
which have, have covered in the deep dive course as well.
Those are even advanced concepts.
Uh, at that level, I don't really expect them to ask you,
but for the sake of completion, I've included, okay?
But this video so far, the last one, super important, okay?
Now, I have shared the code
below the previous video or about the previous video.
You can take a look there and practice it.
Now, this incremental processing was set for the job,
which process data from raw to curated.
We gotta do the same thing from curated to the
aggregated related job as well, right?
That code is, I will be attaching it below
or about this video.
Now you get it done, okay? It's the same thing.
Whatever we did for the previous one, it's the same thing.
You'll just give a try and get it done.
And I know some of you are not doing the hands-on yet,
so there's a prob in English.
You can lead a horse to the water,
but you can't make it drink.
Think about it. You can lead a horse, horse to the water,
but you cannot make it drink.
All I can do is gently nudge you, motivate you.
That's all I can do. I cannot really force you.
So my so motivation for creating this program is that
no matter where you are in your life, what stage of
life you are in, what at what point of life you are in,
what journey you are growing through,
you are here in this program,
and I want you to get full benefit out of it
and really crack those high paying jobs, right?
And, and make your life prosperous.
That said, a few of you, I'm sure have done this hands on.
And for you guys, if you really wanna reinforce the concepts
that you have learned so far,
whatever notes you have taken down,
write them down in the video below
before seeing others comments, and then see
and compare with what others have written
and see how you have failed.
Do that and then go to the next video. Talk to you soon.